You probably have a child out there you
don't know about.
>> Okay. Can I ask this honestly?
>> Yeah, I I I think I have a child,
>> but she denies it.
>> She denies it. She says it's somebody
else, but I her child has
>> Does you seem to have lived quite the
life in your younger years? Did you ever
go with a dude?
Um
I think no no comments but uh I
>> I was I was doing
>> I was experimenting with some things
when I was 16.
>> I I I'll admit to that I was experience
experimenting with some things when I
was 16 but
>> it just did it didn't really
>> I had to I had to figure out
>> everything through
I
>> had to figure out everything through
experience, you know, is it like this?
Is like that. I didn't know who I was.
>> But um by doing so, I also found out,
you know, what I didn't really Yeah. It
just wasn't really didn't feel right,
you know. So,
>> can't know if you're gay unless you try
it, right?
>> Exactly. That's how I felt about it at
the time. and you know somebody you know
there was a guy that wanted to be with
me and so I just let it happen and then
I never you know it was certainly not
something for me
>> their first bird forever.
>> So there you go. I know I'm not gay and
I have no uh I don't have any, you know,
like I'm not insecure about it because I
know I'm not like I know experiment
experientially
I'm not gay because I just it wasn't
interesting
>> at Kitty Style. Did you let the guy suck
your balls?
Uh
>> I'm not going to comment on sort of what
happened.
>> George didn't make you gay. Prison must
suck.
Yeah, if you're not gay. Yeah, it's
pretty lonely.
You'll probably have company if you're
No. Um,
>> don't worry about the trolls. Tongue
sticking out.
>> It just it just felt wrong. Like I don't
know what to say. It just didn't feel
right. It was It was nothing like like I
No, just no. I don't think I I would
ever go out with a with a guy again.
>> But why did you [__] a dude's [__]
It felt wrong to be abused. Well,
congrats. That's how you know you're not
gay.
>> Yeah. So there I can say with confidence
I'm not gay because he simply was not.
>> Tell this story, kitty.
>> I could tell you a million times I'm not
gay and I'll be right every time because
I know
>> he older or younger.
>> He was the same age as me.
Maybe I got raped by my best friend.
>> Is it as good as a chick if you dress
him like one?
I got drugged and raped by my best
friend.
>> Shoot his picture.
>> I have no proof of that.
>> Like a martyr.
>> I have no proof of that. But he did he
did try to drug me. That's kind of
[__] up.
>> Implying sucking dick is fun. Oh well,
wait. That twists the story a bit. D.
>> Yeah, I don't think I've told you this.
I had these uh
I had these suspicions.
>> So this bag tried to drug you?
>> Yeah. Did the balls touch? It's not gay
if the balls don't touch.
>> Yeah, somebody tried to drug me. I
passed out in
>> style. Did you ever get tested for HIV
after the anal sex?
>> H
>> Oh [__] that's kind of [__] by him.
Shh.
>> Well, let's just put it like this. He
always wanted me to
>> like a gay dude.
>> He He seemed pretty gay, but he had a
girlfriend.
>> Trans aren't gay.
>> He seemed pretty gay, but he had a
girlfriend. And he there's clearly
something that he he was holding back,
you know. He never wanted to talk about
girls.
>> You're stuttering.
>> He he thought that
is it bad now.
>> Well, so he thought it was gay to be
with girls. I mean, just he never really
wanted to talk about it. So, it's just a
little bit
>> No, you're good.
>> It's just weird, you know.
>> Style look into the bug chasing and
giftgiving scene.
>> I know. I know.
>> May need to be tested for HIV.
>> Why?
Why? What's the signs and symptoms of
it? I don't think I have it. Wouldn't I
show signs and symptoms of that? When
would you show that?
>> So, he raped you.
>> Well, I don't know what happened, but um
I can tell you this story if you want.
>> I can tell you the story. So, it was
like this. We were smoking some sore in
the morning after.
>> We we were smoking something
um I don't know what it was. It was like
weird.
And then I was like getting like really
high. I was like, "Holy [__] what the
[__] is this?" You know, and so I'm like
I'm I'm getting up and then I get to the
kitchen. I pass out and I wake up on my
stomach in the kitchen
>> and I don't understand how I got there.
>> Man, you gay.
>> Did you find sticky white liquid in your
anal cavity?
>> Lol. Let's just say let's just say that
I uh I went out with his mother and I
told her.
>> Wow. Did you tell anyone?
>> I told her.
>> Or have you been holding
>> I told her but she couldn't she couldn't
she couldn't believe her shoulders.
>> She couldn't believe it.
>> You [__] the dude's mother at kitty
style. You will feel better about this
after a good O fashioned [__] drag.
>> No. How we deal with he did this [__]
first.
>> So you [__] his mil mom but then he
[__] you. No, no, he he [__] her
first.
>> You [__] her mother as revenge for him
raping you. He [__] his momo.
You are a degenerate.
Veilen so hot.
>> He was abusing her. He her son was
abusing her for money and [__] like that
and extorting her. And so I made her
stop doing that to him and I made her
see what
>> his mother too.
>> No, no, no. But I made her see what he
was doing to her and how he he was
abusing her.
>> Was a cacap. Come on.
>> And so I I like he he tried to kill me.
He tried to come to my apartment and
kill me. And I had to jump the window
from the second floor.
I did a heroic jump. It was even caught
on camera. You can see it just I'm just
coming down on a table. I'm just walking
away from the table like just from
second floor. I'm like jumping down and
then you can see me just walking away
from it. I just drove up from second
floor cuz he was he was in my he was he
was in my apartment with a with a pole
with a iron pole. He was he was breaking
into my he was coming in my [__]
front door with an iron rod.
>> How funny.
>> And he kicked in my [__] door in my
living room. He He smashed down
everything in my apartment. He broke
into my home like that.
>> I had to jump the [__] window
otherwise he was going to [__] kill
me with a iron rod, bro.
with an iron rod.
>> Because of
>> come in my front door with an iron rod.
>> His lover was jealous.
>> Why was
>> surprised? Because you [__] his
mother.
>> Well, maybe he shouldn't have raped me.
>> And kick bubblegum. And I'm all out of
bubble gum.
>> Maybe maybe he shouldn't. Maybe he
shouldn't have abused his own mother.
Maybe he shouldn't, you know, maybe he
shouldn't have done those things. So
>> you gay man. His boner was so hard.
Kitty is a madlet.
>> How does it feel when you're gay for
your best friend and then your best
friend dates your mom?
>> Kitty is a based homosexual.
Godamn kitty lmfao
at kitty style. I can PayPal you money
for an HIV test since it sounds like you
may have had an exposure.
>> Abusing mother equals taking advantage
of mother's money. You raped, he will
[__] He
>> He stole uh he stole her her laptop and
computers and things like that. She
stole he even stole me.
>> He stole a lot of things from her home
and he just sort of like he he was just
locking himself into the house and doing
things like he was just he was really
not just abuser like he was really bad
to his mother. She was crying half of
the time because
>> he was just abusing his own mother and
he was he was on heroine. You understand
that? Like he was he he read satanic
books and [__] like that. Like he is
>> there's something wrong with this dude.
>> And I I keep on
>> I help him by teaching his mom what uh
what what what
>> he was really about. What was going on?
>> Your wasn't a satan
>> at kitty style. Sounds like this guy
probably sold access to his anus and was
sharing drug needles with other homos. I
would get checked out.
>> Yeah, if it happened, I don't know.
>> So, it was that uni kebab friend. How
old was she? And you?
>> That's irrelevant.
>> A [__] Well, the way you tell this
story, I'm surprised you weren't the
top. You got raped by a Harian junky
satanist.
>> Maybe. I don't I just don't know because
I don't have any recollection of it.
>> Or a natural skimmed Vlad.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm I'm skinny by natural
nature. I'm naturally skinny. Yeah. So,
>> he don't know what went down. Just that
his ass was on fire the other day. Well,
to bring it back to a positive light,
that sounds like the last time someone
[__] with you at a land party. Maybe.
>> Don't mess with me. And I don't I don't
take it very well.
Nah, let's just say
>> mess with the kitty.
>> Yeah,
>> he will abuse you. Mess with the bull.
You get the HIV. Did he finish inside
you?
>> Are you going to [__] Omar's mom?
>> First, I have to figure out where he
lives.
Oh, [__]
>> Anybody?
Man on a mission.
>> He lives in Finland.
>> I just just joking. No. Yeah. All right.
>> Tell her to send Bobs over Facebook.
>> He's going to be so pissed. No, I'm I'm
not going to do it. I'm not going to do
it.
I'm not going to do it. I'm I'm like I'm
done messing with people like that. You
know what I mean? Like no dirty tricks
no more. No. You have the best [__]
stories. Holy [__] man.